Soon...
Hurry up and come to me.
There they are!
Let's fight to our hearts' content!
You crazy devil.
We won't let you have our Forest of Ente!
I like your spirit.
Don't let me down, now.
Gellen got the best of the auxiliary gates.
He'll get to kill lots.
Oh?
Huh, you came alone?
Oh, how you underestimate me.
You can beg and cry to
be killed all you want,
but I won't be so quick to
put you out of your misery.
I wasn't about to let
anyone else take you on.
I will make you wither myself.
The Battle of the Demonic Realm Portal
Keep your distance and used ranged attacks.
Energy Bolt!
Hmph, you won't wound me
with such meager attacks.
We know that.
Aim for the joints!
Fall back!
Gaia Strike!
Wait, what?
That was more powerful than usual.
Celina?!
Why are you here?
Didn't you head for the main gate?
I left it to Dolan and Chris.
Sheesh.
All our planning was for naught.
This magic... The lamia from yesterday?
That was a pretty powerful spell.
You will be fun to devour.
R-Right back at you. I'll be
the one swallowing you whole!
Will Celina be all right?
Every one of those demons
were absurdly strong.
I know she's with Gio's squad, but still...
Honestly, I think it will be a rough battle.
I won't waver anymore.
But I also want to support
her effort to change.
You really trust her.
Regardless, I'm still worried.
Maybe I should go back.
It'll be fine.
I gave Celina a special magic crystal.
It will assist her in battle.
Also, that girl is strong.
Stronger than she believes, even.
If you say so.
But no, I'm still worried!
We're arriving at the next auxiliary gate!
Weak, far too weak!
This isn't very satisfying!
Get off. I'll run the carriage into him.
G-Got it!
Dolan, you head for the
main gate as planned.
Let me handle this.
Understood.
Who goes there?!
I will be your opponent.
Are you unhurt?
Y-Yes!
Look for a chance to escape.
Take as many survivors with you as you can.
Right.
So it's you, superhuman.
I wanted to fight that human
male more, but you'll do.
I'll let Georg have him.
My apologies. But I'm in a hurry myself.
Awaken, El Spada!
Let's enjoy this battle of life and death,
superhuman!
Oh? You're good.
Way to go, superhuman.
That again? I don't know anything
about this superhuman malarkey.
I don't have to worry about Chris.
But I want to minimize casualties
among all the troops.
I should hurry.
When will you deem it appropriate
to fight me yourself?
Now should be a good time.
Very well. I'll play with you.
This will prevent any outside interference.
We can go at it without worry.
How thoughtful of you.
You're trying to blow away my mist, are you?
I'm glad to see you've learned. Very smart.
But you know what?
I can also use the lives
I've absorbed this way.
Did you just throw their life energy at me?
Life is all powerful.
You just have to use it right.
Like this!
Well? Don't your friends'
lives make quite the impact?
Impressive, isn't it?
How dare you!
You'd better take their
lives into your arms!
A mist that absorbs life energy...
It's too bad.
I can absorb life energy while
simultaneously using it.
Good. Resist with all you have.
I want your suffering to
last as long as possible.
Because that brings me joy!
I'm not about to be your plaything!
The color black absorbs
and embraces everything.
Roses with black petals are
flowers that bewitch all.
Oh? Could it be?
I had sealed this power away,
but you are a worthy—
no, a filthy enough opponent that
I don't have to hold it back.
Ah, so you have the same power I do.
How amusing. Time for a race, then.
Let's see who can absorb
the other's life first!
You were all talk.
That's a nice look.
You came to challenge me alone,
and you'll wither away all alone!
How does it feel to have your life
slowly seep out of your body?
You've absorbed quite a lot of my life energy.
It should be flowing all
through you by now, I believe.
It feels incredible.
Irresistibly delicious.
The spice of your hatred perfectly
accentuates the flavor.
I want to taste this every day if I could!
I'm glad you like it.
Because it's the last
thing you'll ever taste.
Enjoy it while you can.
What are you saying—
What? Where's this pain coming from?
What the heck?!
Why are roses blooming from my body?!
This battle was decided
before we even began.
What?
Ow! It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Do you remember when I attacked you
with a thorn in yesterday's battle?
I sowed some tiny, tiny black
rose seeds in you then.
You never expected an attack
to come from within, did you?
Ah, no... How vexing!
Don't suck my life away!
I am the princess of flowers, meant to
absorb all life and bloom brilliantly...
I managed to defeat her,
but I don't think I could even beat
a woodman sapling right now.
This is bad news.
Energy Rain!
What?
Dolan?
Huh?
Why am I...
Celina? Celina!
I-I just cast a spell...
And then I blocked with Earth Shield...
Huh? I couldn't block it?
Celestial Javelin!
You're awake.
What is this magic circle?
One of defense and healing.
As long as you're in it, it will heal you
and protect you from outside threats.
Thank you.
I also owe you for your help earlier.
Don't worry about it.
So you really aren't human.
Hm? Oh, you mean these?
I am human.
It's just, I have my soul from
my past life—that of a dragon.
I've never even seen a real dragon,
and here I'm meeting one reborn first.
You should lie down for a while longer.
I don't have the time for that.
I know. So I'm sorry,
but I'll be going ahead.
I'll go with you.
I'm going to fly there.
You probably wouldn't
be able keep up.
I can go with you, if you carry me.
Frankly, I'd find it easier
to fight Georg by myself.
How cold.
Not that I need to worry about
you, but please do take care.
Thanks, I will.
No, that's not what I'm worried
about when it comes to you.
Take care not to use too much of
your power and destroy the forest.
Very well. I'll be careful.
I wish you luck.
That's right. Don't let him get any closer.
Yeah, you got it.
Hang in there, Celina! You'll be okay!
Fio?
Why does she sound so worried?
Huh? I feel really...
Don't look, Celina!
Brother!
Yeah, hold her down!
I'll cast a painkilling spell on her.
No way... Celina, you can use healing magic?
Hey, he's getting closer!
This is bad.
Listen well, Celina.
Keep going straight,
and you'll exit the forest.
Huh?
Keep going straight, and don't look back.
We want you to escape at least.
Escape by myself? I can't do that.
Please. I don't want you to die.
So run away.
Eat this!
How many more cuts must
I make to take you down?
That's a superhuman for you.
Your abilities are no joke.
Seriously, what are you talking
about? What is a superhuman?
What? Are they not well-known
in the human realm?
I see how it is now.
I'll tell you.
Superhumans are monsters that are born
among the frail humans in rare instances.
They are superior to ordinary humans
in power, magic, and intelligence.
And the humans can't stand having
such extraordinary people around.
Of course they'd ostracize them.
What would you know, demon?!
Oh? Did that strike a nerve?
Superhumans were our natural enemies.
Despite being mere humans,
they've killed demons, fallen gods,
and even the most powerful ancient dragon.
That's right. The hero who
killed the ancient dragon...
He was a superhuman.
I've been waiting for you.
I never expected to be able
to fight one of them myself!
So I'm one of those spoken of in that song.
Now show me your hero's power!
You have my thanks.
You've helped me understand.
This power of mine...
exists to defeat the likes of you!
So this is what a hero is capable of...
I wonder how the dragon felt when
he was killed by such a monster.
It's obvious.
The dragon counted the
hero among his friends.
And that friend betrayed his trust.
He must resent him for that.
Ever since I saw my former master,
War God Ardes, and you fight together,
I have wanted to cross swords with you.
A battle addict that fell
into the demonic realm, huh?
You dare to challenge me, knowing who I am?
As I must, as a wicked spirit
obsessed with life and death.
Perish lamenting your own powerlessness.
Now that you are reborn as a human,
my sword may be able to
pierce through your heart.
Surely you cannot use your
full power in these lands.
Come.
Allow me to guide you to our demonic realm.
Next Episode
This week's lucky item is black rose!
Look forward to next time!